<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Yaoma Xenotype- The Jade Sisters</name>
	<author>Zomuro</author>
	<supportedVersions><li>1.5</li></supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>Zomuro.ItsSorcery</packageId>
			<displayName>It's Sorcery!</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/Zomuro/ItsSorceryFramework/releases</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3013487115</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>Zomuro.ItsSorcery</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<packageId>Zomuro.YaomaXenotype</packageId>
	<description>"My daughters... I made you as you are. Fashioned your bones fragile as glass, perfected your skin into moonlight, entwining your lifeblood like rubies... All so you may take my teachings."
	
"Hark! Who is the cry of a newborn babe? The festering wounds of a foolhardy solider? The relentless march of an endless plague upon kin? Oppresive and omnipresent, know me as your challenger!"

"Hear me! The archons shall pierce their veils, bringing soulless wrath. Void of my guidance... all will be lost amongst the endless stars."
	
Created by a being interested in defending against a (supposedly) incoming archotech incursion, the Yaoma are intended as the uplifters of humanity.
With unknown conditions now satisfied, they have been scattered amongst the universe with the solar wind, ready to fulfill their purpose.

By the immortal jade.

Features:
	New research tree! Develop the equipment and items of the Yaoma, and marvel at their wonderous effects. wip
	Magic system inspired by xianxia (Chinese high fantasy)! The key to Yaoma perpetuity. Find your Dao, and wield frighteningly powerful abilities. wip
	Three tiers of Yaoma weaponry! wip
	Three tiers of Yaoma apparel! wip
	New charms and shield belts! wip
	New drugs, for war and peace! wip
	Two new storytellers (Farseer Fan and Kaiyi of Karma)! wip
	Two new end conditions! wip
	New AI! wip

My warmest thanks go to:
	Halno, for doing apparel, weapon, and drug art!
	Erok031, for providing building art!
	SirLalaPyon, for crafting mote and icon art!
	Sovereign, for drug, item, and building art!
	Gouda quiche, for patiently helping me with the C# of the magic system and being my mentor!
	Fraudecon, for helping with C# and ability development!
	Argon, for all those night providing C# advice!
	And many others within the RimWorld community for your support!
	
	</description>
</ModMetaData>